<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Grace on Joy Lin</title><link>https://remilarius.github.io/project/tags/grace/</link><description>Recent content in Grace on Joy Lin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://remilarius.github.io/project/tags/grace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://remilarius.github.io/project/grace/blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://remilarius.github.io/project/grace/blog/</guid><description>Hi Grace, this is a page hidden in my website. I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone can find this unless they look in my repo or know to type /grace. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll use the other website for pictures so I can just write here.
I usually address my writing to a hypothetical somebody, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think this changes much for some reason. This is what the voice in my head usually sounds like.</description><content>&lt;p>Hi Grace, this is a page hidden in my website. I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone can find this unless they look in my repo or know to type /grace. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll use the other website for pictures so I can just write here.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I usually address my writing to a hypothetical somebody, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think this changes much for some reason. This is what the voice in my head usually sounds like.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Sorry for being a bit weird earlier, you kept asking whether or not I was in class and I didn&amp;rsquo;t answer a few times. I have a habit of doing that. I think you can tell by the omission the answer to your question.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="things-i-want-to-grace-but-i-dont-want-to-bother-her-right-now">Things I want to Grace but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bother her right now.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>04/13 - I had a GoogleMeet with the JFE HR lady and it was alright. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she thought I was punching down trying to get an internship at JFE. She said the only intern at JFE was the president&amp;rsquo;s son.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>04/14 - I hope you&amp;rsquo;re going to be okay with those injuries. Headaches aren&amp;rsquo;t fun. I got on the roof of Clav today. I had brought my lockpicks to have a go at it but the door was open. I walked around for a bit and explored the machinery. Wave hello to the construction workers on the scaffolding around Randolph.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>04/20 - I would not trade the present for the past, I still don&amp;rsquo;t regret the time I spent with you, but I wonder if I had realized the dire straits I was in and taken a break, if you would still be waiting here for me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>05/19 - Getting interships in Texas and living out there for a year doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound to bad honestly. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if there&amp;rsquo;s anything down there for you though.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="musings">Musings&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s the fact that I can&amp;rsquo;t get a good grade on exams, it&amp;rsquo;s the fact that it feels like I can&amp;rsquo;t bring myself to do thing I should be capable of.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My mind drifts towards infinty, time commits such cruelties.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s just me against the world in every way and I&amp;rsquo;m alone. I&amp;rsquo;m alone and I&amp;rsquo;m so tired.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="things-to-watch-with-grace">Things to watch with Grace&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Suzume no Tojimari&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How to Train your Dragon&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The Thieves&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Love, Death, and Robots&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="things-to-do-for-grace">Things to do for Grace&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Buy her a mechanical keyboard&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Carve a zhuanghe for her (Done)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="places-to-go-with-grace--co">Places to go with Grace (&amp;amp; Co.!)&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Encore Casino &amp;amp; Hotel&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The Arboretum&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ProvinceTown&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fishkill/Poughkeepsie&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item></channel></rss>